=== like post ===
Contributors: behzadazand
Author URI: http://hanet.ir
Plugin URI: http://hanet.ir/like-post
Donate link: http://hanet.ir/donate
Tags: behzad azand, like, wish list, wishlist, interesting posts, like-post, like post, افزونه لیست علاقه مندی ها
Requires at least: 4.7
Tested up to: 4.8
Stable Tag: 0.1
License: GPLv2 or later
License URI: http://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl-2.0.html

A simple plugin for collecting a list of favorite posts for users of news sites or blogs

== Description ==

This plugin allows users of news sites, blogs, or personal to get a list of their favorite posts in their dashboard. By installing this plugin, an item named My favorites will be added to your admin menu. In addition, at the bottom of each of your posts you will add a blue heartbeat image that will be saved to your favorites list by clicking on that post and the red heart image will be red. Also, on the My Favorites page, you can delete the post from your favorites list. This plugin is for news sites and blogs.

If you have suggestions or bugfixes for the plugin, please report them on [my website](http://hanet.ir).

**Languages**

This plugin has been translated into the following languages:

1.Fa

If you want to translate the plugin into your language, [contact me](http://hanet.ir).

== Installation ==

1. Activate the plugin
2. Go To Favorite post and press to blue heart bottom of post content 
3. Go on your dashboard page and see the post in favorit page in admin menu
4. Take a coffee and relax, you did a great job!

== Screenshots ==

1.like post panel


== Changelog ==

= 0.1 =

* First release!

== Upgrade Notice ==

= 0.1 =

* First release!